calgarypuck.com 2017-08-07

# Calgarypuck.com » Privacy

### Privacy Statement for Calgarypuck.com

Calgarypuck.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We will not provide or sell user-specific demographic information to any other person or business. We will only share this information on an aggregate basis.

Our site uses cookies (user data collectors). We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Opt Out").

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, however we do not guarantee this protection and assume no responsibility for that information.

### Children’s Guidelines

This site collects personally identifiable, online and offline contact information from all users interested in participating in contests, product offerings and other specific activities on this Web site. In some cases this information is more than is necessary to participate in the given activity. This site also gives all of its users the ability to read and to post in public forums. The site does not have a filter in place to exclude children from these activities without prior parental consent. Calgarypuck.com uses its best efforts to make the content of its Web site acceptable for family viewing although younger children should be supervised.

### Policies for Children Under 13

Safeguarding the personal information of children is extremely important to us. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the site. No information should be submitted to or posted at Calgarypuck.com by children under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact boardadmin@calgarypuck.com.
